<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>William Lam</title>
    <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme" />
    <updated>2021-03-17T00:57:05-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Bill Lam</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme</id>

    <entry>
        <title>About Me</title>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lam</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/about-me.html"/>
        <id>https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/about-me.html</id>

        <updated>2021-03-17T00:57:05-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    As a volunteer coach for neighborhood robotics teams since 2010, I've had the honor of working with 62 talented kids through 130+ competition events spanning 28 robotics campaign seasons. We have been blessed with great kids that aspire for greatness and have won over 55&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a volunteer coach for neighborhood robotics teams since 2010, I've had the honor of working with 62 talented kids through 130+ competition events spanning 28 robotics campaign seasons. We have been blessed with great kids that aspire for greatness and have won over 55 awards, with 10 at the national level. In my daytime endeavors, I'm a global sales manager for a technology solutions company, where I meet amazing engineers around the world who have a passion for making the best possible products. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learning takes place in three locations: our makerspace, robotics competition venues, and STEM outreaches to underrepresented and disadvantaged communities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A majority of our teams work in our makerspace programming robots, discussing teamwork, good stewardship, and core values of who/what we are. At robotic competition venues, students learn the merits of teamwork as they pair up to compete against other pairs of teams. Until COVID our teams typically complete about 10 outreaches per year to help promote robotics and STEM to underrepresented and disadvantaged communities.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I have a BSEE/MS-IT/MBA and worked at AT&amp;T Bell Labs. In the last 16 years years have been in technical sales. I grew up and started working in our family restaurant at age 7 and continued helping for the next 22years. I saw how difficult life was for people without college degrees. Although not in full time philanthropy, I have always had a desire to help others.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Exit 6 Robotics</title>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lam</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/exit-6-robotics.html"/>
        <id>https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/exit-6-robotics.html</id>

        <updated>2021-03-16T00:52:55-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Exit 6 Robotics was founded in 2017 and is currently active. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Exit 6 Robotics was founded in 2017 and is currently active. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Exit 5 Robotics</title>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lam</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/testing.html"/>
        <id>https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/testing.html</id>

        <updated>2021-03-16T00:51:55-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Exit 5 Robotics was founded in 2010 and still active and collaborating with Exit 5A Robotics.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Exit 5 Robotics was founded in 2010 and still active and collaborating with Exit 5A Robotics.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Exit 5A Robotics</title>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lam</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/hello.html"/>
        <id>https://williamplam.github.io/aboutme/hello.html</id>

        <updated>2021-03-16T00:52:13-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Exit 5A Robotics was started in 2014 and currently is active today, collaborating with Exit 5 Robotics.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Exit 5A Robotics was started in 2014 and currently is active today, collaborating with Exit 5 Robotics.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
